welcome back to my channel hello friend
the uk best car insurance company
revolta 2021 okay afford the award has
50 000 uh customer marketing the biggest
insurance focus survey server under the
award is not category
there is the 10 award winner is the
category is no over
one and this this
satisfactions of the best care incidents
company climb satisfactions
[Music]
satisfactions and this
and the coco can jewelry
[Music]
domestic and proper insurance direct
line
and live bank ms
mns bank and and view module
of ris and
saga
customer certifications the best
insurance company
in the in the uh
kingdom and the rises of the whole
subject
will win says and this
best best instruments car of company for
customer
[Music]
uh best in united kingdom
is the shayna wheels and century bank in
ln
bank and censors
and the best car incidence company based
on customer recommendations of the
uk united and
united kingdom this this is
best of very high people's
his service is
actually uses this uh insurance
for cars
um very uh different different types of
categories and she uh sherlock wheels
and best
car companies customer recognize and
viva coco insurance direct line
and saga and celebrity
and banks disco banks best
[Music]
how to cut important insurance
best car insurance company for the
customer
satisfaction viewer is this
uh sa and viewing which ones
are iss credits and
sagashi levels uh best
united kingdom is the rules
and limitations how to use this
car driving and this
important these ones the best
instruments
uk and this
what is the national speed the limit in
the uk
the national speed limit in the uk
depends on what type of
vehicles you drive within
two we kill three uh two vehicle and
four weekends six because
long cars and a small
bike motor motorcycle like this
this this one you watch for your system
water circles it was
a vehicles double vehicles and the car
for
because when you conditional speed limit
is 3.30
mph or 40 kilometers hours
a single climb 60 mp 96 gamma
hours is the national speed limit is the
different you the
doing of the women's style beauty and
clears
10 ampere perform simple
five five mph 80 kilo
80 km per gateway system
opening a good insurance is not only
about a low price
like this is good but response
and like easy
like and share please subscribe